English	Chinese	Korean	Japanese
Administrator	管理员	관리자	管理者
please input 6 nunber	请输入6位数	여섯 자릿수 입력해주세요.	6桁の桁を入力してください
password incorect	密码有误	비밀번호가 틀렸다	パスワードが間違っています。
			
Rent Locker 	出租柜	임대료 보관함	家賃ロッカー
Pink Color Boxes are not available.	粉红色的盒子是不可用的。	분홍 색 상자 사용할 수 없습니다.	ピンクの色の箱は利用できません。
Big Lockers - $10.00/2hrs	大储物箱每两小时10￥	대축하다.	大容量箱は2時間当たり10￥
Small Lockers - $5.00/2hrs	小储物箱每两小时5￥	소축물상자는 두 시간 5 시간이다.	小箱は2時間ごとに5￥
"This box is unavaliable, please select another box."	该箱子无效，请选择其他箱子	이 상자는 무효입니다. 다른 상자를 선택하세요	この箱は無効になり、他の箱を選択してください。
Enter your date of birth as a 6 digit pin number	输入您的出生日期作为6位PIN号码	입력한 출생 한 여섯 자리 비밀번호	6桁のピン番号として誕生日を入力してください
Exmaple 02/01/88	示例 02/01/88	예시 2 / 0 / 1 / 8	例02 / 01 / 88
Please select payment method	请选择支付方式	지불 방식 선택	支払い方法を選択してください。
Amount due	到期金额	금액	金額
please insert notes	请插入注释	넣으십시오 노트	ノートを挿入してください
already paid:	已付：	이미:	既に支払いました：
exit pay	退出支付	수출 임금	出口賃金
please insert your credit card and enter password	请插入您的信用卡并输入密码	신용 카드 넣으십시오 암호를 입력하십시오.	あなたのクレジットカードを入れてパスワードを入力してください
the box is open now	箱子现在打开了。	지금 이 상자 열기	その箱は今開いている
"please remember your box number and password,close door after use"	请记住您的箱子号码和密码，关门后使用	"부디 상자 몇 및 비밀번호 사용 후, 문"	お使いのボックス番号とパスワードを忘れないでください
			
"This box has not been rent, please select your rent box."	箱子未被租用，请选择您的租用箱	"상자 가 임대 되지 않으니, 임대 상자 를 선택해 주십시오"	ボックスがレンタルされていませんので、レンタルボックスを選択してください。
usage expire or payment didn't complete. you need to pay another: $ 	使用期限或付款未完成。你需要支付另一美元：	사용 또는 지불 기간이 완성할 수 없다.너는 반드시 다른: $	使用期限や支払いが完了しなかった。もう一つ支払う必要がある
continue use	继续使用	계속 사용	使用を続ける
end use	结束使用	사용 끝	使用を終了
